Thank you for watching.
May I ask you to take a dip in the ocean?
The Sound of the Sea in the Sea
Yes!
Once the horses are in, we can make a course for the future.
Wow, yay!
I'm from Tochigi, so I don't have a ruff.
Oh no!
I'm flying too fast!
I was really stupid.
Thank you very much for watching!
Staff, please go to the staff!
Please wait!
It's tough to run with a camera.
I don't have anyone here with me.
The manager I was running with was worried about me because of the lame way I was running.
Doesn't your back hurt from the way you're running? He said.
I guess it was lame. The way I was running. I'm going to study this more from now on.
He was very encouraging, but I felt like...
Hey, you're making fun of me! You're making fun of me!
I know, right! I can't describe it, but it's amazing!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Like that?
Games! Games!
Like this? Like this?
Yes, sorry.
So I knew it was single-minded.
But first of all...
First of all, Luna, as the oldest, led us,
Talman, as the oldest and most important one, led us,
And then the third and seventh were the new Yuna,
The third and the seventh are the new Yuna, and the new Yuna sees everyone very clearly,
So, I mean he is supporting us,
The rest are Mi-yu Tsujiki and Ii, who are in charge of the big songs,
and Amu, Senna's son, is the oldest of all the members and he is doing his best,
The last of the three is the leader, Anni.
I'm tired.
Some high school boys on bicycles.Some high school boys on bicycles.
Go for it! something like that.
Wow!
Thank you! He said.
What's your name? and say...
I'm in a group called One Love One Heart.
I'm an artist.
Thank you very much. I said, "Thank you very much.
That was close.
You did your best.
That was a close one.
20 minutes?
It's so cold!
One.
Oh, no.
This way, this way.
Then you still heard the sound of an opening.
Yeah, it sounded like a whoosh.
Oh, I got a "eech" sound.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I couldn't get that sad look on Iitch's face out of my head.
We all had to see Eechi's
Eechi.
Oh, my God.
Do you usually run?
Not at all.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry.
But this time, when I decided to run, I did it once.
But my muscles were sore and I couldn't move.
I didn't run enough.
I finished in one day.
But the leader of today's last run...
He ran 12 kilometers in practice.
But he said his legs were all sore because of it.But he said it made all his legs sore.
I practiced this too. With my mom. Practiced running and drinking.
I mean, it's bad that I went to Haruma.
Oh, no! Haruma is bad.
Did you have fun?
You can go! Good luck! I was so excited to hear that.
Wow! That's great!
You're a good guy, Haruma.
Come on! Fight!
That's great, Yunagi.
Are you okay?
They'll all be here in about 5 minutes.
Great.
You love her so much.
It's good to have you here, Haru.
Really?
Thanks!
Now that you said it's reassuring, I'm off!
Run the whole thing through.
It's great!
I can do it, I can do it! You're so fast!
You really only say things that motivate me! That's rare!
At a time like this!
We're doing great! Really fast!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on.
Cute, cute, cute.
All right, here we go.
We'll be at 500 after this.
We'll pass the last hurdle.
Be careful... you don't want to roll over.
I can't get it out. I can't get it out.
You don't have to.
You're already fast enough.
You've run almost 10 kilometers.
I'm sure they'll all be out by now. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.Let's go let's go!
Go, go, go!
It's 100! I'm on it!
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Good work!
Ukisho, Ukisho, keep going.
Ukisho, go, go, go!
Ukisho, go, go!
[End]
I had a feeling that it was really hard work,
But, you know, everyone was so amazing,
I really respect them more and more,
I love the members so much.
I feel really sorry for being so late,
But everyone covered for me, and everyone was amazing, really amazing,
I was so impressed by how great everyone was, and I really love you all!
Yes, I was running with them, but I was also thinking about the members,
In the latter half of the race, Isshin encouraged me all the way, and I was able to finish the race safely,
I really think it was thanks to all of you. It was a lot of fun! It was a great experience!
I was just trying my best to do my best, and in a moment of time I was doing my best.
I felt like I was doing my best in the moment, and everyone was like, "Wow!
When everyone said "wow" from the location bus...
I was so happy to see you guys during the break.
It really, really cheered me up.
I felt glad to be alive.
So it was fun.
I'm a little disappointed that I missed my goal time by a little bit, but everyone was so supportive of me.
But I'm really grateful for everyone's support, and I was able to finish the race.
But my breathing got a little unsteady towards the end, and I was having a really hard time, but everyone was behind me today, so...
I was really tired, but I was able to take a step forward because of the way you guys were running.
I'm really happy that I was able to pass the baton to Anny in one piece, and it was a great memory for me.
It wasn't an easy road for me.
I'm sure it wasn't an easy road, but now that I've crossed this stage, I'm going to step up to the next level and keep walking upward.
I hope I can go one level higher and keep moving forward.
I think it was an experience that made me realize that there is a difference between running 10 kilometers by yourself and running 10 kilometers with the support of your friends.
If it weren't for my friends, I wouldn't have been able to run.If it weren't for my friends, I really wouldn't have been able to run.
Yes, it's true... straight to Tokyo Dome like this...
I really want to catch it.
Please wait for me!
Cool!
The 100 km anniversary was a great success!
Yay!
We're all going to Tokyo Dome!
Wow!
Kaito Miyachika, the second YouTube project!
Yay!
Yay, yay, yay!
Oh, it's hot!
Woo hoo!
Wow!
Wow.
Swish.
Gush
And make a mess.
People can't tell if it's burnt or not.
It's so delicious!
Wow.